UX/UI DESIGNER

PRECIOUS ENWEREM

4379287832

<u>enweremprecious16@gmail.com</u>. <u>https://www.linkedin.com/in/precious-enwerem-246871170</u> https://precious-enwerem.herokuapp.com/

A highly creative and innovative UI/UX designer based in Toronto, Canada, with the determination to learn and enhance my design skills. I aim to help clients achieve their goals and create meaningful experiences and opportunities through my designs.

SKILLS

Software

- Adobe XD
- Figma
- Canvas
- Illustrator
- In Vision
- Sketch

Others

- Story Boarding
- Flow Chart

Design

- Design Research
- User Interface
- Prototyping
- Wireframing
- Web Design
- Interaction design

EXPERIENCE

FEBRUARY 2022 - PRESENT (PART-TIME CONTRACT)

UX/UI DESIGNER, SIPHLE

Siphle is a start-up software development company that creates lucrative websites for companies. As the UX/UI designer, my core activities include:

- o Gathering and evaluating user requirements with the help of my teammates.
- Researching, and creating wireframes, site maps, user flow diagrams and prototypes using InVision and Adobe XD.
- Creating and presenting hi-fi prototypes for Davito services website using Adobe XD.
- Completing tasks before my given deadline.

JANUARY 2022 - PRESENT

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE, BILL GOSLING OUTSOURCING

Bill gosling outsourcing is an outsourcing and account management service based in Newmarket, Canada.

- Answering probing questions to customers and providing advice over the phone.
- o Identifying and solving problems while providing technical and troubleshooting support.
- Handling inbound calls in a professional, efficient and courteous manner.

OCTOBER 2021 – DECEMBER 2021

UX/UI INTERN, KREER

Kreer is a business development company based in Lagos, Nigeria. As an intern UX/UI designer, my core activities included:

- Designing the look and feel of the website's contact page according to my supervisor and the client with a two-week deadline using Figma.
- Working and learning closely with the junior and senior UX designers to create an easyto-navigate website for our client.
- o Attending and contributing to design process meetings.

EDUCATION

2012 - 2018

WEST AFRICA SENIOR SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE EXAMINATION, CALEB INTERNATIONAL SCHOOL, LAGOS, NIGERIA

2018 - 2019

DIPLOMA, GREAT LAKES COLLEGE OF TORONTO

2021

UX DESIGN CERTIFICATE, GOOGLE UX CERTIFICATE